Thanks for calling Ace Dentists. I'm Liv. How can I help?
Hi, Liv. I need to book an appointment for my son. He's got a toothache he's been complaining
about and yeah, he just needs an appointment ASAP.
Is your son experiencing any swelling, uncontrolled bleeding, trauma, or trouble breathing or
swallowing? No, none of that. Just that he's complaining about his toothache is causing him
a headache and things of that nature. I just want to get him checked out, make sure it's
nothing too serious. Got it. Is this your son's first visit with us or has he been to the
practice before? It would be his first time. Thanks. May I have your son's full name and
the best phone number to reach you on? His name is Malachi. Malachi Adams.
Thanks. And the best phone number to reach you on? That's [phone number hidden]. Do you have a preference
for a day or time for the appointment, morning, afternoon, or any time? I mean, it's pretty
bad he's been complaining. Is there any slots for today back in the evening maybe?
There are no regular appointment slots left today, but I do have some emergency slots tonight
with an emergency call out surcharge. I can offer 930, 10 in the evening or 1030. Does
any of those times work for you? Yeah, we can do 930. 930 works. Thanks. Is your email address
available or would you prefer not to provide it? I prefer not to provide it. I don't think
it's necessary. To confirm, I have booked a new urgent dental assessment appointment
for Malachi Adams on Tuesday the 6th of October at 930 in the evening with the emergency call
out surcharge. The best number to reach you on is [phone number hidden]. Is that all correct?
Yep, that's all right. Thank you. The appointment is all set for Tuesday the 6th of October
at 930 in the evening. The team has everything they need. Thanks for calling Ace Dentists
and I hope Malachi feels better soon.